https://www.framesgallery.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentWe are delighted to announce that there is now free shipping within the UK
Privacy PolicyIf you visit our gallery, exhibitions or events: What we collect…WhyLegal BasesWe may collect your name, postal address, email address and phone numberWe would like to keep you up to date with news about our exhibitions and eventsWe will only send you these communications via email if we have your consent to do soBank detailsWe require these details to process the sale.We do not receive these details if you pay online or by card in our Gift shops. Any information you provide to us over the phone will be securely destroyed.This is required for the contract (sale of the product or service)If you subscribe to our email invitation list:We may collect your email address and communication preferencesWe would like to keep you up to date with news about our work, events, products, special offers and ways of supporting National Museums ScotlandWe will only send you these communications via email if we have your consent to do soIf you consent to receive information by email, your email address and communication preferences are held by MailChimp, which is the email marketing system we use to send out our e-newsletters, and they are used only for the purpose of sending you these communications. You can choose to opt out of these marketing communications at any time by contacting us at info@framesgallery.co.uk or by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of every e-newsletter.If you use our website:In order to make the Frames Gallery website easier to use and improve our service, we sometimes place small amounts of information on your computer. These are known as cookies and they are used by most major websites. You can find out more about Our use of cookies here.Sharing information:We do not disclose personal data to any third parties or external organisations, other than companies carrying out work on our behalf.  We retain responsibility for your data and ensure that these organisations only act on our instructions.Examples of when we share data:Email marketing services (eg Mailchimp)We may occasionally need to transfer your personal information overseas, for instance to our email marketing provider, MailChimp. We ensure any transfers of data are secure, in accordance with best practice, and in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation. You can read the MailChimp Privacy Policy here.Your data will never be sold or passed to any third party for any other purpose.How we keep your information secure:We have implemented security procedures, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:Unauthorised accessImproper use or disclosureUnauthorised modification.All our employees and data processors, who have access to and are associated with the processing of personal data, are legally obliged to respect the confidentiality of the personal data that we hold.Your Data Protection Rights:Under new data protection laws taking effect in May 2018, you have rights in relation to your personal data. These rights are:The right of access: you have the right to know whether we are processing any of your personal data. If we are, you have the right to access the data and certain information, such as why we are processing the dataThe right of rectification: you have the right to ensure that we correct inaccuracies in your personal data that we are processingThe right of erasure (the ‘right to be forgotten’): in certain situations you have the right to ensure that we erase your personal dataThe right to restriction of processing: in certain situations you have the right to ensure that we restrict our processing of your personal dataThe right of data portability: in certain situations you have the right to receive personal data that you provided to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable formatThe right to object: in certain situations you have the right to object to our processing of your personal data and we are normally obliged to stop processing your data when requested. This right includes the right to object to our processing of your personal data for the purposes of direct marketingThe right to complain: you have the right to make a complaint to the UK Information Commissioner’s Office(ICO) about our processing of your data, the exercise of your rights, and other data protection mattersThe right to withdraw consent: you have the right at any time to withdraw your consent for us to process your personal data.These rights are not absolute and may not apply in all situations or in relation to all processing activities.Requests to exercise any of these rights should be sent to:Frames Gallery 10 Victoria Street Perth PH2 8LW Email: info@framesgallery.co.uk.At any time you may request that we delete or correct your personal information by simply contacting info@framesgallery.co.uk.
...
This site uses cookies: Find out more.Okay, thank you
